adit-media.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy policy - Adit-media

Buya Media Ltd. (“Buya”), as owner of the website acting under the domain name www.adit-media.com (the “Website”), under which You can register and receive Our Services, respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use our Services. This privacy policy statement (“Privacy Policy”) explains which information we collect/may collect, and how we use it.

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of our Terms and Conditions, as applicable. 

**Personal Information**

Personal information is information such as your name or mailing address that can be used to uniquely identify you. In order to get our Services and/or to receive newsletters or commercial offers, You must provide personal information. All your personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, email address, is held in strict confidence. This information is collected for the primarily purposes of enabling you to receive the Services requested by you, but may also be used, from time to time, to provide you with newsletters or commercial offers. We do not sell or share personal information in a form that can identify you to any other party.

**The Data Base**

The information you provide when registering to the Services download will be stored in Our data base. You are not required by law to provide the information but without providing the same you will not be able to use certain of our Services.

**Information Collection and Use Practices** **  
** Please note that our Services collects information about your activity in both anonymous and personally identifiable forms. We use information about your way of activity on this Service to improve our products and services; and we may share with our partners aggregated and non-personally identifiable information regarding the way our users use the Services. You hereby irrevocably waive any claim with regard to Us collecting the information mentioned above.

For the purpose of this section, Non-Personal Information shall mean any information that cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity. Non-Personal Information includes but is not limited to your configuration with respect to our Services. 

**Email communication**   
Please note that during the registration with the Services you are requested to provide a valid email address in order to enable the registration process, to enable our team to provide you with email support (as applicable) and in order to allow Us to contact you, from time to time, via email communication, with news and updates about services, products and offers (such as: a newsletter, new releases, new features, special offers etc.).   
  
If you wish, at any time, to remove your email address from any of the above mentioned email mailing lists and stop receiving future email communications from Us, other than the emails directly related to the Service functionality, you may unsubscribe by an email to: [contact@adit-media.com](mailto:contact@adit-media.com). For your convenience, email communication from Us contains instructions regarding how to unsubscribe from Our e-mail mailing lists.

**Cookie Policy**

If you choose to use our web-site without blocking or disabling cookies, you will indicate your consent to our use of cookies and the collection of any personal information that we collect using cookies. If you do not consent to the use of cookies, please be sure to block or disable them using your browser settings.

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. These text files can be read by these websites and help to identify you when you return to a website. Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer when you have gone offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to block and delete cookies, please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org/](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

We use our own cookies to recognize you when you visit our website. This means that each time you visit, and we can remember your preferences and settings.

**Applicable Privacy and data protection Laws**

The privacy protection and data protection under the Agreement shall be in accordance with the laws of the State of Israel. Users from other jurisdictions, which jurisdictions might have in place, or legislate in the future, any rules and regulations more restrictive, or differently applied, from those applicable under the laws of the State of Israel, shall be aware of such differences, if any.

Please feel free to send us any questions you may have regarding this statement.
